[Adapted from Che Ye Liu Xiang's
novel of the same name]
[Episode 3]
Big Bro. Stop it.
You're going to kill him.
That enough, Young Master Lin?
Whatever Xiao Fan says goes.
Let me tell you something.
My coattails aren't for just anyone to ride.
Leave Lu Xiao Fan alone from now on.
You got that?
Get lost.
What's with all the bags?
I...
I was going to lay low for a while.
Go back.
Zi Yang.
Is he going to die?
Relax.
Those guys are the old man's people.
They know how to hold back.
We could beat him for two hours
or even four hours
and the kid still wouldn't die.
Quit showing off.
All right. I still gotta walk someone out.
I'll head out first then.
Thanks, Zi Yang.
Let's go.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Big Bro, I'll just go put my stuff away.
Lu Xiao Fan.
Why are you such a doormat?
They pick on you, and you never fight back?
Even if you won't fight back,
can't you at least tell me?
I didn't want to cause you trouble.
So, you still caused trouble, didn't you?
You know what to do from now on?
Yeah.
You little brats.
All you do is pick fights and cause trouble.
Just you wait till I report this
to the dean's office.
Hey, is that him?
Keep your voice down.
That guy's under the protection of Bei.
The one who bullied him before?
Bei had him beaten up.
It doesn't stop there.
Not even a week later,
his expulsion was finalized.
Bei really dotes on his sidekick.
Xiao Fan.
Oh, there you are.
Everyone's here. Let's go.
Come on.
Zi Yang.
I can't take this any more.
You guys go on without me.
Hey.
Don't go.
So?
I got back at them for you. Satisfied?
Let me tell you.
Lv Qing's never been this showy
all his time at school,
not even me.
Just to get you a few hands,
I caught hell from the old man at home.
Thanks, Zi Yang.
Don't thank me.
Thank your brother.
All right. Quit gloating.
Fine. Now that all the trouble's over,
your brother and I will take you out to relax.
Go easy on me! It hurts!
Lu Xiao Fan, come on.
Can't you grow a spine for once?
Lu Xiao Fan.
Grow a spine, will you?
So nice.
What's wrong?
Lu Xiao Fan.
I brought you here to unwind,
but you're just here learning others' tricks.
Big Bro.
Does it feel the same?
Big Bro, whenever you're tired, just call me.
No sense wasting money here.
Aren't you tired?
Not at all.
Lu Xiao Fan.
You're unbelievable.
Still can't let go of your cardboard, huh?
Xiao Fan.
There's another box over there.
Bei.
Still hyped up?
Lu Xiao Fan.
Someone's on the phone for you.
For me? Who is it?
Said she's your wife.
- Here.
- Stop bringing this trash inside.
Lu Xiao Fan.
Hello?
Come on, everyone! Let's party!
Three stars shine, five champs rise!
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Eight horses!
Kiss!
- Come, come, come.
- Lu Xiao Fan.
- Get over here.
- Who's that?
Hey, Fan! You're here.
Go ahead, grab a seat.
Come, come.
Join us, join us.
Come on! Have a drink!
A toast to Fan!
Here, Fan.
Another sip, yeah?
Go on.
- Drink, drink.
- Lv Xin.
You should go home early.
Louder.
Go home early.
Take me home later.
- Go on, eat up!
- Go on, eat.
Eat up.
- Have one!
- Try one!
Have one! Have one! Have one!
Drink it down.
Swallow.
Swallow it, swallow it.
Swallow!
He swallowed it!
That's hilarious. All I see is money.
Lv Xin.
I don't feel so good.
Come on, have some more.
Let's go to bed.
We're home!
Hey, pretty boy.
- I wanna go home.
- Where are you off to?
Where are you off to, handsome?
Let go of me.
Settle down.
Xin is here.
All the best, handsome.
Hey, Big Brother.
I'm having a party.
Come join us.
Come have fun, Big Bro.
- Come play with us.
- Guess who's here with me.
Who else could it be?
I'm going to fuck Lu Xiao Fan.
- What are you doing?
- Help me.
Help you?
- What's this?
Strip. Take it off.
Take them off.
Look at his Adam's apple. Still so young.
Wow, such fair skin.
So youthful, handsome.
And who's this?
Haven't seen him before.
He's pretty handsome.
So, this is what it takes
for my brother to finally turn up.
Well, since you're here,
why don't you strip too?
Go on, strip.
Take it off. What are you waiting for?
Since you're already crazy, push it further.
Come on, shoot your brother too!
If you don't strip,
I'll kill him.
Strip!
Hurry up! What are you waiting for?
Strip.
Let him go first, and I'll take off the rest.
Where's the key?
The keys!
Get lost.
Get her to the hospital.
Xin.
Let's get you to the hospital.
Big Bro.
Am I going to die?
Lu Xiao Fan.
You did this on purpose.
That thing of yours hasn't been used yet?
Big Bro.
Don't...
Compared to women,
you prefer getting screwed by men, don't you?
Big Bro.
What? No more water from Lu Xiao Fan,
and you're left with nothing to drink?
Nothing better to say, huh?
Big Bro.
The kid was a virgin,
and just like that, he lost his virginity.
I mean...
All right, fine.
It's none of my business.
Xiao Fan.
Get in.
Ever wonder why ancient
noble young masters all had a page?
Well, think about it.
When boys are at an age for studying,
they're also full of youthful passion.
By the old rule, men and women
avoid physical contact.
Getting entangled with women
would ruin one's good name.
Your brother always
has people fawning over him.
Not everyone deserves his devotion.
Some things feel light as a feather
till you weigh them.
Once on the scale, they weigh a ton.
Lu Xiao Fan.
I know that you're not stupid.
Thank you, Zi Yang.
I don't blame him.
All right.
Mom.
How's everyone been lately?
Oh, so you still remember to call.
Aren't you at the same school as Bei Lv Qing?
Must be easy for you two to meet up.
Your big brother's job is no good.
There's no future in it at all.
When you see Lv Qing,
ask him to help make arrangements.
[Male Dormitory]
Compared to women,
you prefer getting screwed by men, don't you?
Who is it?
Come in.
Big Bro.
I brought you some hot soup.
Xiao Fan.
Now that you're in Yunjing,
don't go forgetting your family.
We must not climb the social ladder
and turn our backs on our roots.
Does it still hurt?
I'm...
I'm much better.
I'm sorry, Big Bro.
Take off those wet clothes.
What happened?
Is it about your brother?
Wasn't that job good for him?
The Beis have helped us plenty.
We can't keep imposing on them.
I...
My brother, he...
He said he wants to come to Yunjing.
Okay.
I'll take care of it.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
Big Bro.
The cafeteria food is way too salty.
I'll continue bringing you soup.
Won't it be a hassle?
Not at all.
Big Bro, I'll head back then.
Come on!
Lv Qing.
Why are you so distracted?
This isn't your usual form.
Let's go.
Once we finish, let's get a nice meal.
I'll pass today.
I won't go today.
You can't focus on this right now.
Then what should I be looking at?
I've taken care of your brother's matters.
Don't worry.
Big Bro.
Someone will be here soon.
Scared?
Why are you hiding?
Didn't you cry in my arms yesterday?
I'm just afraid someone might see us.
That's not what I meant.
What's this?
The key to my apartment.
Big Bro, it's fine.
It's quite convenient staying at school.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm moving into my apartment.
And you're coming with me.
Did you put off moving out
because of my daily soup runs?
Lu Xiao Fan did not know
what all that had passed
between him and Bei Lv Qing
these days truly meant,
nor what it had changed.
But somehow,
being permitted to attend
to Bei Lv Qing's daily needs
filled Xiao Fan with a sense of honor.
Two. Three. Four.
Two clay pots.
Soy sauce.
Big Bro.
You're back.
What soup are we having tonight?
Oh, I made winter melon and spare rib soup.
Big Bro, I got a really good cut of ribs today.
Good.
I also picked up some household stuff.
I don't know what brand you use.
So, I just grabbed whatever.
[Call Me B.Duck]
That one? I bought it on sale.
I didn't look closely at the brand.
You sure...
you want me to use this?
You don't have to.
I'll just keep it for myself.
Let's bathe together.
The soup's burning.
The soup's going to burn.
Here.
Big Bro.
Try it, quick.
Have a taste.
Well?
Not bad.